<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Hugo website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Amazon&#39;s Stock Price</title>
      <link>/2017/06/18/stock-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/18/stock-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Stock News   Objective: To analyze and forecast closing prices of Amazon Inc.’s (AMZN) stock using machine learning extrapolatory algorithms. Data: The data has been extracted from quantmod package. I have used AMZN stock’s closing prices for the past 2 years. For further details on quantmod visit: http://www.quantmod.com/
 Loading required packages  Plot showing 5 year historical stock price chartSeries(AMZN$AMZN.Close)  Smoothing data to take the average of every 21 days (trading days in a month) close.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s The Magic Sauce For A Great Data Scientist?</title>
      <link>/2017/06/17/analyzing-dj-patils-article-building-data-science-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/17/analyzing-dj-patils-article-building-data-science-teams/</guid>
      <description>How To Become A Data Scientist Technical expertise: the best data scientists typically have deep expertise in some scientific discipline. • Curiosity: a desire to go beneath the surface and discover and distill a problem down into a very clear set of hypotheses that can be tested. • Storytelling: the ability to use data to tell a story and to be able to communicate it effectively. • Cleverness: the ability to look at a problem in different, creative ways</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Word Clouds using Twitter API</title>
      <link>/2017/06/08/ixperience-word-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/08/ixperience-word-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Word Clouds using Twitter API iXperience Word Cloud iXperience Word Cloud
 I’m going to show you how to build a Word Cloud using the latest tweets you’re interested in. As a part of iXperience’s intensive Data Science program, I was naturally interested in visualizing some of the words that are associated with “iXperience”. In order to create these beautiful Word Clouds, one has to first get access to Twitter’s API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raghav&#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>/2017/06/06/raghavs-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/06/raghavs-blog/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin Price Fluctuation &amp;amp; Prediction My first blogpost is about predicting Bitcoin currency value. Fun Fact: An investment of $30 in Bitcoin in 2009 would be worth $1,000,000 today!
 Bitcoin Historical Prices
 Since Bitcoin Prices are very volatile and do not carry a clear trend and seasonality, it was hard to predict accurate future values. This was especially true when trying to predict using a large amount of historical data, such as a five-year horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a Blog created by Raghav Kumar dedicated to Data Science.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>